I couldn't wait for you to come and clear the cupboards
But now you're gone and leaving nothing but a sign
Another evening, I'll be sitting reading in-between your lines
Because I miss you all the time
So, get away
Another way to feel what you didn't want yourself to know
And let yourself go
You know you didn't lose your self-control
Let's start at the rainbow
Turn away
Another way to be where you didn't want yourself to go
And let yourself go
Is that a compromise?
So, what do you wanna do?
What's your point of view?
There's a party, screw it
Do you wanna go?
A handshake with you
What's your point of view?
I'm on top of you
I don't wanna go
'Cause I really wanna stay at your house
And I hope this all works out
But you know how much you broke me apart
I'm done with you, I'm ignoring you
I don't wanna know
And I'm aware that you were lying in the gutter
'Cause I did everything to be there by your side
So, when you tell me I'm the reason
I just can't believe the lies
And why do I still want to call you?
So, what do you wanna do?
What's your point of view?
There's a party, screw it
Do you wanna go?
A handshake with you
What's your point of view?
I'm on top of you
I don't wanna go
'Cause I really wanna stay at your house
And I hope this all works out
But you know how much you broke me apart
I'm done with you, I'm ignoring you
I don't wanna know
I don't know why I'm no one